A Guide to the Edgar B. Young papers FA109
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Lincoln Center, Inc., 1952-1980 (1956-1976); 1956-1976; 1; 26.48 Cubic Feet 68 letter document boxes, 1 legal document box, and 1 flat file folder; 69 Boxes 27.6 cubic feet
  - Planning and Construction, 1956-1978; 9
    - Philharmonic Hall - Acoustics - Young's Analysis of Beranek's Article, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 728)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Building Improvement, 1962-1963 (1971) (Box 57, Folder 729)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Building Improvement, 1964-1967 (1971) (Box 57, Folder 730)
    - Philharmonic Hall - General Files, 1956 (1971) (Box 57, Folder 731)
    - Philharmonic Hall - General Files, 1957 (1971) (Box 57, Folder 732)
    - Philharmonic Hall - General Files, 1958-April 1959 (1971) (Box 57, Folder 733)
    - Philharmonic Hall - General Files, May 1959-March 1960 (1971) (Box 57, Folder 734)
    - Philharmonic Hall - General Files, April 1960-June 1961 (1971) (Box 57, Folder 735)
    - Philharmonic Hall: Plaza Level, Scheme B6, 1960 April-1961 June; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 7)
      Separated from Series 1.9 Planning and Construction, Box 57, Folder 735
    - Philharmonic Hall: Plaza Level, Scheme A5, 1960 April-1961 June; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 7)
    - Philharmonic Hall - General Files, July-December 1961 (1971) (Box 57, Folder 736)
    - Philharmonic Hall - General Files, 1962 (1971) (Box 57, Folder 737)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Green Room, 1962-1965 (1971) (Box 57, Folder 738)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 21.
    - Philharmonic Hall - Green Room, 1964-1965 (1971) (Box 57, Folder 739)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Harrison and Abromowitz Meetings Minutes, 1957-February 1959 (Box 57, Folder 740)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Harrison and Abromowitz Meetings Minutes, March 1959-1960 (Box 57, Folder 741)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Opening Night, 1961-September 17, 1962 (1971) (Box 58, Folder 742)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Opening Night, September 19-22, 1962 (1971) (Box 58, Folder 743)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Opening Night, September 23-December 17, 1962 (1971) (Box 58, Folder 744)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Opening Night and Opening Week, August-September 1962 (1971) (Box 58, Folder 745)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Opening Week, 1960-1961 (1971) (Box 58, Folder 746)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Opening Week, February-August 1962 (1971) (Box 58, Folder 747)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Opening Week, September-November 1962 (1971) (Box 58, Folder 748)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Organ, 1956-April 1958 (1971) (Box 58, Folder 749)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Organ, September 1958-April 1959 (1971) (Box 58, Folder 750)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Organ, May 1959-March 1962 (1971) (Box 58, Folder 751)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 22. Architectural material has been removed and is housed separately.
    - Philharmonic Hall, Lincoln Center, 1959 May 9; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 7)
      Separated from Series 1.9 Planning and Construction, Box 58, Folder 751
    - Philharmonic Hall - Organ, May 1962-March 1966 (1971) (Box 58, Folder 752)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Seating Capacity, 1960-1961 (1971) (Box 58, Folder 753)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Stage Alterations, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 754)
    - Relocation - Braislin, Porter & Wheelock - General Files, January-March 1957 (1971) (Box 58, Folder 755)
    - Relocation - Braislin, Porter & Wheelock - General Files, January-May 1958 (1971) (Box 59, Folder 756)
    - Relocation - Braislin, Porter & Wheelock - General Files, June-December 1958 (1971) (Box 59, Folder 757)
    - Relocation - Braislin, Porter & Wheelock - General Files, January-April 1959 (1971) (Box 59, Folder 758)
    - Relocation - Braislin, Porter & Wheelock - General Files, June 1959-August 1960 (1971) (Box 59, Folder 759)
    - Relocation - Braislin, Porter & Wheelock - The Schorr Report, November 30, 1959 (Box 59, Folder 760)
      Final Report (March 4, 1969).
    - Relocation - Property Management and Construction, 1958-January 1959 (Box 59, Folder 761)
    - Relocation - Property Management and Construction, April 1959-1960 (Box 59, Folder 762)
    - Repertory Theater - Library Building Opening, 1964-1965 (1971) (Box 59, Folder 763)
    - Repertory Theater - Library/Museum Conference, July 19, 1962 (Box 59, Folder 764)
    - Reports - Hart, Krivatsky, Stubee Feasibility Study, undated (Box 60, Folder 765)
    - Booklet "Feasibility Study for U.D.C." Lincoln Center, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 14) (Drawer D 14, Folder 8)
      Separated from Series 1.9 Planning and Construction, Box 60, Folder 765
    - Reports - Project Status, April 1961-July 1962 (1971) (Box 60, Folder 766)
    - Reports - Project Status, March 1963-March 1965 (1971) (Box 60, Folder 767)
    - Television Facilities, November 1959-January 1963 (1972) (Box 60, Folder 768)
    - Travertine - All Buildings, April 1963-June 1964 (1971) (Box 60, Folder 769)
    - Vivian Beaumont Theater - Design and Building, 1957-1959 (1971) (Box 60, Folder 770)
    - Vivian Beaumont Theater - Design and Building, 1960-1961 (1971) (Box 60, Folder 771)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 23.
    - Vivian Beaumont Theater - Design and Building, 1962 (1971) (Box 60, Folder 772)
    - Vivian Beaumont Theater - Design and Building, January-September 1963 (1971) (Box 60, Folder 773)
    - Vivian Beaumont Theater - Design and Building, October 1963-1964 (1971) (Box 60, Folder 774)
    - Vivian Beaumont Theater - Design and Building, January-June 1965 (1971) (Box 60, Folder 775)
    - Vivian Beaumont Theater - Design and Building, July-September 1965 (1971) (Box 60, Folder 776)
    - Vivian Beaumont Theater - Design and Building, October 1, 1965-June 1966 (1971) (Box 60, Folder 777)
    - Vivian Beaumont Theater - Design and Building, July 1966-1968 (1971) (Box 60, Folder 778)
    - Vivian Beaumont Theater - Design and Building, 1970-1973 (1971) (Box 60, Folder 779)
  - Public Relations, 1955-1973; 10
    A formal public relations campaign was initiated in 1959 to increase the community awareness of the existence of Lincoln Center and to develop recognition within the society that Lincoln Center was built to serve the arts, entertainment and educational interests of the general public.
    Newspaper clippings (1955-1963) and press releases (1956-1964) are available. Lincoln Center's role as the performing arts arm of the New York World's Fair (1964-1965) is also documented.
    Public Relations press kits help illuminate two important events in the history of Lincoln Center. The first is a press kit from January 20, 1959 announcing the inclusion of Fordham University in the Lincoln Square Urban Renewal Project. Following public and legal opposition to the use of government funding to support a non-secular institution (which eventually resulted in the U.S. Supreme Court dismissal of the case), Fordham University purchased the land from West 60th to West 62nd Street between Columbus and Amsterdam Avenues and built housing for their Law School and Liberal Arts College. As the owner of its own land and facilities, Fordham University is a neighbor in Lincoln Square adjacent to Lincoln Center, but is not a constituent of Lincoln Center and was never offered, nor eligible, for such status. (Correspondence and legal documents regarding this Church-State Issue are available in Subseries 9 - Planning and Construction.) The second is a press kit from the Lincoln Center Groundbreaking Ceremony on May 14, 1959, attended by President Dwight D. Eisenhower, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Robert Moses, New York Mayor Robert Wagner and New York Lt. Governor Malcolm Wilson.
    - Annual Reports, 1959-1963 (Box 61, Folder 780)
    - Annual Reports, 1967-1971 (Box 61, Folder 781)
    - Audience Surveys, 1963-1968 (1972) (Box 61, Folder 782)
    - Brochures - Samples, circa1961 (Box 61, Folder 783)
    - Carnegie Hall - Legislation to Save Carnegie Hall, 1958-1962 (Box 61, Folder 784)
    - Clippings, April 1955-March 1957 (Box 61, Folder 785)
    - Clippings, April-July 1957 (Box 61, Folder 786)
    - Clippings, August-September 1957 (Box 61, Folder 787)
    - Clippings, October-November 1957 (Box 61, Folder 788)
    - Clippings, December 1957-February 1958 (Box 61, Folder 789)
    - Clippings, March-April 1958 (Box 61, Folder 790)
    - Clippings, May 1958 (Box 61, Folder 791)
    - Clippings, June-October 1958 (Box 61, Folder 792)
    - Clippings, November 1958-February 1959 (Box 62, Folder 793)
    - Clippings, March-June 1959 (Box 62, Folder 794)
    - Clippings, July-December 1959 (Box 62, Folder 795)
    - Clippings, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 796)
    - Clippings, 1961-June 1963 (Box 62, Folder 797)
    - Earl Newsom & Company, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 798)
    - Earl Newsom & Company, January-March 1961 (Box 62, Folder 799)
    - Earl Newsom & Company, April 1961-1965 (Box 62, Folder 800)
    - General Files, 1956-May 1957 (1973) (Box 62, Folder 801)
    - General Files, June-December 1957 (1973) (Box 62, Folder 802)
    - General Files, January-March 1958 (1973) (Box 62, Folder 803)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 24.
    - General Files, April-May 1958 (1973) (Box 62, Folder 804)
    - General Files, June-July 1958 (1973) (Box 63, Folder 805)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 25.
    - General Files, September-December 1958 (1973) (Box 63, Folder 806)
    - General Files, January-September 1959 (1973) (Box 63, Folder 807)
    - General Files, October 1959-1960 (1973) (Box 63, Folder 808)
    - General Files, January-May 1961 (1973) (Box 63, Folder 809)
    - General Files, June-October 1961 (1973) (Box 63, Folder 810)
    - General Files, 1962 (1973) (Box 63, Folder 811)
    - General Files, 1963 (1973) (Box 63, Folder 812)
    - General Files, 1964 (1973) (Box 63, Folder 813)
    - General Files, 1965-1966 (1973) (Box 63, Folder 814)
    - General Files, 1967-1968 (1973) (Box 63, Folder 815)
    - General Files, 1969-1972 (1973) (Box 63, Folder 816)
    - Groundbreaking Ceremony - Clippings, May 14-15, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 817)
    - Groundbreaking Ceremony - General, May 14, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 818)
    - Groundbreaking Ceremony - Press Kit, May 14, 1959 (Box 64, Folder 819)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 26.
    - Guided Tours, 1963-1969 (Box 64, Folder 820)
    - Guided Tours, 1960-1969 (Box 64, Folder 821)
    - "Holiday" - v. 44, n.3, September 1968 (Box 64, Folder 822)
    - Library/Museum of the Performing Arts - Proposal Kit, October-November 1961 (Box 64, Folder 823)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 27.
    - Lincoln Center Festivals, 1963-1968 (Box 64, Folder 824)
    - Lincoln Center Films, 1958-1959 (Box 64, Folder 825)
    - Lincoln Center Films, 1960-1961 (Box 64, Folder 826)
    - Lincoln Center Neighborhood, March 1958-August 1961 (1971) (Box 64, Folder 827)
    - Preliminary Plans and Schematic Elevations, Lincoln Square Plaza, 1960 March 21; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 7)
      Separated from Series 1.10 Public Relations Box 64, Folder 827
    - Lincoln Center neighborhood, 1958 March-1961 August; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 7)
    - Lincoln Center Neighborhood, 1963-1971 (Box 64, Folder 828)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 28.
    - Lincoln Center Neighborhood, October 1961-May 1965 (1971) (Box 64, Folder 829)
    - Lincoln Center Neighborhood, 1966 (1971) (Box 64, Folder 830)
    - Lincoln Center Neighborhood, January-September 1967 (1971) (Box 64, Folder 831)
    - Lincoln Center Neighborhood, October 1967-August 1968 (1971) (Box 65, Folder 832)
    - Lincoln Center Neighborhood, November 1968-1973 (1972) (Box 65, Folder 833)
    - Lincoln Square Community Council, 1960-June 1968 (1972) (Box 65, Folder 834)
    - Lincoln Square Community Council, July 1968-February 1971 (1972) (Box 65, Folder 835)
    - Lincoln Square Community Council, March 1971-March 1973 (1972) (Box 65, Folder 836)
    - Miscellany, 1961-1967 (1978) (Box 65, Folder 837)
    - Miscellany, 1968-August 1971 (1972) (Box 65, Folder 838)
    - Miscellany, September 1971-September 1972 (1972) (Box 65, Folder 839)
    - Miscellany, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 840)
    - National, 1958; 1961 (1971) (Box 65, Folder 841)
    - National, 1963-1965 (1971) (Box 65, Folder 842)
    - New York World's Fair (1964-1965), May-October 7, 1960 (1972) (Box 66, Folder 843)
    - New York World's Fair (1964-1965), October 10, 1960-January 1961 (1972) (Box 66, Folder 844)
    - New York World's Fair (1964-1965), May-December 1961 (1972) (Box 66, Folder 845)
    - New York World's Fair (1964-1965), February-April 1961 (1972) (Box 66, Folder 846)
    - New York World's Fair (1964-1965), 1962-1964 (1972) (Box 66, Folder 847)
    - New York World's Fair (1964-1965), 1963-1965 (Box 66, Folder 848)
    - "The Performing Arts" - General Files, 1959-1960 (1970) (Box 66, Folder 849)
    - "The Performing Arts" - Issues, March 12, 1959-April 22, 1960 (1973) (Box 66, Folder 850)
    - "The Performing Arts" - Issues, May 6, 1960-October 27, 1961 (1973) (Box 66, Folder 851)
    - "The Performing Arts" - Issues, November 14, 1961-November 15, 1963 (1973) (Box 66, Folder 852)
    - Philharmonic Hall - Opening of Books, October 2, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 853)
    - Photographs, 1964-1967 (Box 66, Folder 854)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 29.
    - Press Releases - General Files, 1956-May 1958 (Box 66, Folder 855)
    - Press Releases - General Files, June-November 19, 1958 (Box 67, Folder 856)
    - Press Releases - General Files, November 21, 1958-May 1959 (Box 67, Folder 857)
    - Press Releases - General Files, June-December 1959 (Box 67, Folder 858)
    - Press Releases - General Files, January-June 10, 1960 (Box 67, Folder 859)
    - Press Releases - General Files, June 19-December 1960 (Box 67, Folder 860)
    - Press Releases - General Files, January-July 1961 (Box 67, Folder 861)
    - Press Releases - General Files, September 1961-March 1962 (Box 67, Folder 862)
    - Press Releases - General Files, April-July 1962 (Box 67, Folder 863)
    - Press Releases - General Files, August 1962-April 17, 1963 (Box 67, Folder 864)
    - Press Releases - General Files, April 22-August 16, 1963 (Box 67, Folder 865)
    - Press Releases - General Files, September 1963-1964 (Box 67, Folder 866)
    - Press Releases - Kit - Fordham University to Become Part of Lincoln Square, January 20, 1959 (Box 68, Folder 867)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 30.
    - Programming, circa1961-1965 (Box 68, Folder 868)
    - Programming, circa1966-1968 (Box 68, Folder 869)
    - Programming, 1969-1973 (Box 68, Folder 870)
    - Repertory Theater Design - Press Releases and Publicity, November 14, 1961 (Box 68, Folder 871)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 31.
    - West Side Association of Commerce and "The West Sider", 1961-1962 (Box 68, Folder 872)
    - Young's Comments about Manuscripts on Lincoln Center, November 1969 (Box 68, Folder 873)
    - Young's Comments about Manuscripts on Lincoln Center, December 1969 (Box 68, Folder 874)
    - Young's Comments about Manuscripts on Lincoln Center, 1970-1972 (Box 68, Folder 875)
  - Working Files, 1952-1977; 11
    This subseries includes information regarding Edgar B. Young's work as author of "Lincoln Center: The Building of An Institution," New York: New York University Press, 1980.
    The holdings available include various notes, outlines, documentation of interviews, Young's comments regarding the vital importance of the participation of JDR 3rd in the Lincoln Center project, and a revised manuscript written in October 1979.
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - Commemorative Plaque, 1969-1972 (Box 68, Folder 876)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - A Personal Commentary by Edgar B. Young, January 27, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 877)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - Edgar B. Young's Interview with Charles M. Spofford, February 15, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 878)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - Outline, 1976-1977 (Box 68, Folder 879)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - Phase I - Exploratory, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 880)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - Source Material, 1952-1955 (Box 68, Folder 881)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - In Evolution of Concept and Institutional Composition, 1976-1977 (Box 68, Folder 882)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - In Architectural Planning and Construction, 1976-1977 (Box 68, Folder 883)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - List of Lincoln Center Files in Archives, undated (Box 68, Folder 884)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - #3 - In Relations with Government - City, State, Federal, 1976-1977 (Box 68, Folder 885)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - #4 - In Management, 1976-1977 (Box 68, Folder 886)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - #5 - In Public Relations, 1976-1977 (Box 68, Folder 887)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - #6 - In Finance, 1976-1977 (Box 68, Folder 888)
      A. Financial Planning B. Fundraising C. Personal Contributions
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - #6 - In Finance, 1970; 1976 (Box 68, Folder 889)
      D. Rockefeller Sources
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - A. - JDR 3rd Chronology, 1976-1977 (Box 69, Folder 890)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - B. - Relocation and Demolition, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 891)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - C. - Church/State Issue, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 892)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - D. - Visual Arts at Lincoln Center, 1976-1977 (Box 69, Folder 893)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - E. - High School of Music and Art, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 894)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - F. - Educational Television, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 895)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - G. - Lincoln Center Neighborhood Relations, 1976-1977 (Box 69, Folder 896)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - H. - Lincoln Center Labor Relations, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 897)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - I. - New York World's Fair, 1964; 1976 (Box 69, Folder 898)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - J. - Fund for Education and Creative Artistic Advancement, 1976-1977 (Box 69, Folder 899)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - K. - Lincoln Center Operations, 1976-1977 (Box 69, Folder 900)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - L. - Constituents Created by Lincoln Center, 1976-1977 (Box 69, Folder 901)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - JDR 3rd's Role - M. - Juilliard: Carnegie Corporation Grants and Funds for the Drama Division, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 902)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - Young's Manuscript - Edgar B. Young's Schedule, circa 1970s (Box 69, Folder 903)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - Young's Manuscript - Parts I and II - pp. A-1 - 3-30 (Box 69, Folder 904)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - Young's Manuscript - Parts I and II - pp. 4-1 - 5-31 (Box 69, Folder 905)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - Young's Manuscript - Parts I and II - pp. 6-1 - 7-6 (Box 69, Folder 906)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - Young's Manuscript - Part III - pp. 8-1 - 10-25 (Box 69, Folder 907)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - Young's Manuscript - Part III - pp. 11-1 - 12-9 (Box 69, Folder 908)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - Young's Manuscript - Part IV - pp. 13-1 - 13-55 (Box 69, Folder 909)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - Young's Manuscript - Part IV - pp. 14-1 - 16-20 (Box 69, Folder 910)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - Young's Manuscript - Part IV - pp. 17-1 - 18-1 (Box 69, Folder 911)
    - "Lincoln Center: The Building of an Institution" - Young's Manuscript - Part V (Box 69, Folder 912)
- Japan Society, 1973-1978; 2; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes; 3 Boxes 1.2 cubic feet
  This series is arranged into six subseries, each of which are organized alphabetically by folder title:
  Subseries 1 - Administration Subseries 2 - Building Operations Subseries 3 - Education Subseries 4 - Financial Administration Subseries 5 - Fundraising Subseries 6 - Public Relations
  The Japan Society is a private, nonprofit institution founded in 1907, and revitalized in the 1950s through the effort and vision of John D. Rockefeller 3rd, to promote greater cultural understanding and cooperation between Japan and the United States. The Japan Society has developed and sponsored programs in the arts, business, education, and public affairs. These programs often include Japanese art exhibitions, films, performances, a lecture series, public policy research projects, educational fellowships, and sponsored classes in cultural and language studies for children and adults.
  Due to its small size and limited time span, the holdings in this series only give a glimpse of the work of the Japan Society and Edgar Young's role in the organization.
  - Administration, 1973-1978; 1
    The largest of the subseries, Subseries 1 contains a copy of the Japan Society by-laws (1973) and minutes of the Executive Committee meetings (1973-1978).
    - Annual Dinners, Meetings, Retreat, 1974-1978 (Box 70, Folder 913)
    - Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Box 70, Folder 914)
    - Bi-monthly Activities Reports to the Board, 1974-1977 (Box 70, Folder 915)
    - Bi-monthly Activities Reports to the Board, 1978 (Box 70, Folder 916)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1978 (Box 70, Folder 917)
    - By-Laws, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 918)
    - Committee Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 70, Folder 919)
    - Directors and Officers, 1974-1978 (Box 70, Folder 920)
    - Executive Committee Meetings Minutes, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 921)
    - Executive Committee Meetings Minutes, 1974 (Box 71, Folder 922)
    - Executive Committee Meetings Minutes, January-May 1975 (Box 71, Folder 923)
    - Executive Committee Meetings Minutes, June-December 1975 (Box 71, Folder 924)
    - Executive Committee Meetings Minutes, January-August 1976 (Box 71, Folder 925)
    - Executive Committee Meetings Minutes, September-December 1976 (Box 71, Folder 926)
    - Executive Committee Meetings Minutes, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 927)
    - Executive Committee Meetings Minutes, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 928)
    - "Japan-United States Friendship Act", 1975 (Box 71, Folder 929)
    - Nominating Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 72, Folder 930)
    - Program Review and U.S.-Japan Conference on Cultural and Educational Interchange (CULCON), 1975 (Box 72, Folder 931)
    - Executive Search Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 72, Folder 932)
  - Building Operations, 1973-1976; 2